It turns out the correct answer is actually Kimberli.
اتضح أن الجواب الصحيح هو Kimberli في الواقع.
But why? Let's trace the program and see.
لكن لماذا؟ لنتتبّع البرنامج ونرى.
The first thing we do, is we create and initialize this variable size using names.length.
أول ما علينا فعله هو إنشاء متغيّر size هذا وتعيين قيمته باستخدام names.length.
In this case, the size is actually seven.
في هذه الحالة، الحجم هو 7.
Then we create this variable longestName and we initialize it to names of zero,
بعدها ننشئء هذا المتغيّر longestName
which is this value here.
وهي هذه القيمة هنا.
So longestName becomes Anja.
فتصبح قيمة longestName هي Anja.
Then we start our for loop
ثم نبدأ حلقة for ونعين قيمة I الابتدائية بواحد.
And as long as i is less than size, and then we increment by i++.
وما دامت قيمة i أقل من قيمة size نزيد القيمة بمقدار ++i.
So inside our loop, we check if name of i the length is greater than longestName.length.
وداخل حلقة التكرار، نتحقق إن كانت name[i].length &gt; longestName.length.
Names of I in
Names[i] في هذه النقطة هي Kimberli بينما قيمة longestName هي Anja.
This happensaaa to be eight characters long and this is only four,
ويصدف أن طول هذا الاسم 8 أحرف، بينما طول هذا الاسم 4 أحرف فقط،
so this if statement is true.
إذن، عبارة if هنا هي true.
names[i].length, which is eight is greater than longestName.length, which is four.
قيمة names[i].length، وهي 8، هي أكبر من قيمة longestName.length، وهي 4.
So we step inside the if condition and we update
فندخل في شرط if ونحدّث
longest name to be equal to names, which is Kimberli.
قيمة longestName لتساوي names، وهي Kimberli.
We move on adding one to i.
نستمر ونضيف 1 إلى i.
So we're Know checking Edmond,
نتفقّد الآن الاسم ُEdmond.
we do our comparison.
نقوم بالمقارنة.
Edmond's only six characters long compared to eight,
يتألف  ُEdmond من 6 أحرف فقط مقارنة مع 8،
so we do not step into the if condition and we just keep going.
فلن ندخل في شرط if ونتابع طريقنا.
Then we compare Shenna,
ثم نقارن Shenna،
which is also six characters long,
وهو اسم يتألف أيضاً من 6 أحرف،
so it's not greater than Kimberli.
فهو ليس أكبر من Kimberli.
So this if statement is false we do not update longestName and we keep going.
لذا، قيمة عبارة if هذه هي false، فلا نقوم بتحديث longestName ونتابع طريقنا.
Now reach Apolonia, which is eight characters long.
نصل الآن إلى Apolonia، وهو اسم يتكون من 8 أحرف.
So our if statement is saying if names of i, which is Apolonia.length,
إذن، تنص عبارة if على أنه إذا كانت names[i]، وهي Apolonia، ثم .length،
which happens to be eight is greater than longestName.length,
ويصدف أن قيمتها هي 8، &gt; longestName.length
which is Kimberli.length, which is eight.
وهي Kimberli.length، والتي قيمتها 8.
So it's saying if eight is greater than eight, that's not true.
أي أننا نقول إذا كانت 8 أكبر من 8، وهذا غير صحيح.
Eight is not greater than eight,
8 ليست أكبر من 8،
so we do not step into this statement and hence we do not update the longest name.
فلا ندخل في هذه العبارة، وبالتالي، لا نحدّث قيمة longestName.
So longestName remains Kimberli and then we continue
فتبقى قيمة longestName هي Kimberli، ثم نتابع الحلقة
our loop where the remaining two strings are also smaller than Kimberli.
حيث السلسلتان المتبقيتان أصغر من Kimberli أيضاً.
So, by the end of our loop we return the longestName which still has Kimberli in it.
إذن، مع نهاية الحلقة، نعرض قيمة longestName والتي لا تزال تحتفظ باسم Kimberli.
And that's why, in this particular implementation,
ولهذا السبب، في هذا التطبيق تحديداً،
this example would actually return Kimberli.
سيعرض هذا المثال Kimberli.
In a general sense,
وبصفة عامة،
It would return the first longest string it finds.
سيعرض أول أطول سلسلة يجده.
However, another correct implementation of this function could be,
لكن هناك تطبيق صحيح آخر لهذه الدالة،
this check here greater than or equal to.
وهو أن تكون عبارة التحقق هنا أكبر من أو يساوي، =&lt;.
Let's trace this one and see what this would return.
لنتتبّع هذه العبارة ونرى ما ستعرضه.
longestName would be initialized to Anja again,
سيتم تحديد قيمة longestName باسم Anja مجدداً.
and then in our loop we start moving down to Kimberli,
وخلال الحلقة، نبدأ بالانتقال إلى Kimberli،
which is greater than Anja.
وهي أكبر من الاسم Anja.
So, we update that and then we step down again to Edmond,
فنقوم بتحديثه وننتقل مجدداً إلى Edmond،
it's not greater than Kimberli so we just skip that one.
وهو ليس أكبر من Kimberli، فنتخطاه.
Shenna is also not greater than Kimberli so we skip that one.
Shenna ليست أكبر من Kimberli أيضاً، فنتخطاها.
And now Apolonia is eight, Kimberli is eight,
والآن، Apolonia مكونة من 8 أحرف، وKimberli مكونة من 8 أحرف،
so where condition is if eight is greater than or equal to eight,
إذن، يصبح شرطنا: إذا كانت 8 أكبر من أو تساوي 8،
which is true in this case,
وهذا صحيح في هذه الحالة،
so we step inside and we update longestName to names of i, which is Apolonia.
فندخل في الحلقة ونحدّث قيمة longestName لتساوي names[i]، وهي Apolonia.
So longestName gets updated to Apolonia this time.
أي أنه يتم تحديث قيمة longestName إلى Apolonia هذه المرة.
And then we step through Caroll,
ثم نتخطى الاسم Caroll،
and the last name which are both smaller than Apolonia.
والاسم الأخير، فكلاهما أصغر من Apolonia.
So we end up returning that longestName,
فينتهي الأمر بعرض قيمة longestName،
which is this one this time.
وهي Apolonia في هذه المرة.
So a small difference like this check, between greater than,
إن فرقاً صغيراً مثل شرط التحقق هذا، بين أكبر من،
or greater than or equal can make this subtle difference.
وأكبر من أو يساوي، من شأنه أن يُحدث هذا الفرق الصغير.